let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who is the father of C language?",
        answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
        options: [
            "Steve Jobs",
            "James Gosling",
            "Dennis Ritchie",
            "Rasmus Lerdorf"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: " Which of the following is not a valid C variable name?",
        answer: "int $main;",
        options: [
            "int number;",
            "float rate;",
            "int variable_count;",
            "int $main;"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 3,
        question: "All keywords in C are in ____________",
        answer: "LowerCase letters",
        options: [
            "LowerCase letters",
            "UpperCase letters",
            "CamelCase letters",
            " None of the mentioned"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 4,
        question: " Which of the following is true for variable names in C?",
        answer: "Variable names cannot start with a digit",
        options: [
            " They can contain alphanumeric characters as well as special characters",
            "It is not an error to declare a variable to be one of the keywords(like goto, static)",
            "Variable names cannot start with a digit",
            "Variable can be of any length"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 5,
        question: " Which is valid C expression?",
        answer: "int my_num = 100000;",
        options: [
            "int my_num = 100,000;",
            "int my_num = 100000;",
            " int my num = 1000;",
            "int $my_num = 10000;"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: " What is an example of iteration in C?",
        answer: "all of the mentioned",
        options: [
            "for",
            "while",
            "do-while",
            "all of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: " What is #include <stdio.h>?",
        answer: "Preprocessor directive",
        options: [
            "Preprocessor directive",
            "Inclusion directive",
            "File inclusion directive",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which of the following return-type cannot be used for a function in C?",
        answer: "none of the mentioned",
        options: [
            "char *",
            "struct",
            "void",
            "none of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What will be the value of the following assignment expression?  (x = foo())!= 1 considering foo() returns 2 ",
        answer: "2",
        options: [
            "2",
            "true",
            "1",
            "0"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: " What will be the output of the following C function when EOF returns?    int fputs(char *line, FILE *fp)",
        answer: "When an error occurs",
        options: [
            "‘�’ character of array line is encountered",
            " ‘n’ character in array line is encountered",
            "‘t’ character in array line is encountered",
            "When an error occurs"
        ]
    },

];